sinobiological.com 2016-04-26

# aboutTemplate模版

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy aims to elucidate all of the ways we store, process, disclose, secure, and correct the information you provided to the website of Sino Biological Inc. (referred to as “we,” “us,” the “Company” or similar terms). You automatically agree with the Privacy Policy when you visit and use the website for any purpose. All the information provided by your use of the website will be allowed for practices under the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy.

##  Information collection

 We collect and analyze all kinds of information from the visitors to our website for the purpose of sales of products and services, improving the content and services on the website, as well as designing marketing strategy.

##  Non-personal information:

We collect non-personal information such as the URL of the site you just came from, the browser version you use, date/time of access, statistics on page views, and traffic to and from the sites. Your personal information will not be disclosed to us by such data we collect if you merely visit your website without order or registration.

We also use cookies which is a small piece of text stored on a user's computer by a web browser to track session (state maintenance), and remember specific information about users, such as site preferences or the contents of their electronic shopping carts. You may choose to reject cookies by setting the internet browser, but it may cause inconvenience for your experience on this website.

##  Personal information:

If you choose to register on the website, you will complete a form to provide your contact information including your email, name, company or institute, address, location, phone and fax. You may also provide us with your personal information by ordering products or services. The personal information is used for order management, communication of product or service requirement, shipping of products, feedback collection, and advertising.

##  Information treatment

We treat the collected information in different ways according to the type of information involved for the main purpose to offer better services and experience with the website.

##  Non-personal information:

We use the non-personal information stated above to adjust our website navigation, customize the site to your preferences, and help administer the website by analyzing the statistics. We reserve the right to make full use of non-personal information.

##  Personal information:

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to conduct business, provide information and support for products and services, better understand your needs and interests, refine and develop our products and services, personalize communications and ensure a quality experience with our website.

 For instances, we retain your name, address, phone, and credit card number in order to ship your orders and communicate for order details. Besides, we may send order confirmations, shipment notifications, new product release, and promotion news to your email address. We may also notify the account status of our customers and changes to any relevant agreements or policies via email. You can choose what information you would like to receive by contacting us or selecting options.

 We will collect data and analyze statistics for marketing research, product development and other reasonable business purposes and operational efficiency improvement.

 We may share personal information with necessary business partners such as the credit card companies and shipping companies. Without your specific prior consent, we will not disclose your information to unaffiliated third parties other than authorized third parties (such as contractors supporting operation of this site) and other partners cooperated in the e-commerce(e.g., payment, service providers), which may need access to some of your personal information. We ensure such third parties to comply with our Privacy Policy, and limit their access and use of your personal information. Occasionally, we may also disclose personal information if required by law enforcement, government contract administrators, court order, or other legal process.

##  Information Protection

We implement concrete technology to protect the information you provide to us, such as use of encryption, network firewalls. However, we do not guarantee impeccable secure even with necessary procedures. It is your responsibility to safeguard email addresses, passwords as registration information on this website.

##  Information modification

You can change, correct, or delete your information provided to us at any time by logging in your account or by contacting us. You may request to delete your account; however, certain information will still be stored to accumulate order data for legal compliance purposes. We reserve the right to block accounts with false or inaccurate information until it is revised to our satisfaction.

##  Privacy on other websites

This Website may provide links to other websites for your convenience. However, we do not control or supervise the content or privacy practices of the websites administered by other organizations. Therefore, we disclaim all liability with regard to your access to or use of such linked websites. You should refer to the terms and conditions of those websites, including the privacy policies of those websites, when you use the websites of other links.

##  Children's Privacy

This website is designed for adult users, thus we do not intend to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you find that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us by the methods below.

##  User Conduct

You are required to comply with the following user conduct rules. Any misconduct will result in the termination or suspension of your account without refund, even legal suit for severe damage to the benefits of Sino Biological Inc.

You will not intentionally fabricate false information.

You will not use the website in the name of others.

You will not use this website or any products purchased from Sino Biological Inc. for any illegal purpose.

You will not hack this website to steal information or sabotage the functioning of the website.

##  Effective Date

The Effective date of this Privacy Policy is 2009-11-20

##  Revisions to Privacy Policy

We may change the Privacy Policy under reasonable circumstances at any time. Changes will be notified on this webpage.

##  Contact information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or requests with regard to the information you provide to us, pleas contact us by email: order@sinobiological.com
